Russia receives some material
Россия получает какие-то материальные
benefits so it distributes it among
блага так оно распределяет её среди
its citizens so yeah yeah When Russia
своих граждан так угу да Когда Россия
does some kind of nude So who is responsible for this
делает какую-то ню Так кто несёт за это
citizens have nothing to do with it it
ответственность граждане ни при чём да
turns out Good evening I’m from Ukraine, the
получается Добрый вечер я из Украины
city of Khmelnitsky And
город Хмельницкий А
you are Russia Nizhny Tagil
вы Россия Нижний л Тагил
Tagil  from these Yes, but they don’t
Тагил с этих Да только я не
advertise I don’t advertise
афишируют я не афишируют
the special operation,
спецоперацию
support it at all
поддержите вообще
Well, that is, I’m a neutral person,
никак Ну то есть я нейтральный человек
neutral to everything, neutral it’s like
нейтральный ко всему нейтральный это как
to everything Well, that is, let’s say
ко всему Ну то есть есть допустим
There are Ukrainians. There are Russians. There are Americans,
украинцы есть Русские есть американцы
so I have a normal attitude towards them. VS Well, yes,
вот я к ним нормально ВС отношусь Ну да
but now your country is killing people in
но сейчас ваша страна убивает людей в
my country, how do you feel about this?
моей стране вы к этому как относите
Unfortunately Well, with sadness Well, what can be done
К сожалению Ну с печалью Ну что сделать
here? Well, nothing has been done Well, it
здесь ничего не сдела Ну типа нейтрально
turns out to be neutral or
получается или
whatever Well, actually  I’m talking about all this
как Ну на самом деле я вот об этом всем
in general, well, I
вообще ну мне
kind of have it because yes, it’s sad, but
типа есть потому что да это печально но
I’m talking about it in no way. There’s nothing you
я же говорю с этим никак Ничего не
can do. I’m not asking what you can do. I’m asking your attitude to
можете сде Я спрашиваю ваше отношение к
this. Well, this is bad, yes, bad, yes  that is,
этому А ну это плохо да плохо да то есть
it’s wrong for Ukraine
это неправильно на Украину
Yes, maybe I’m not in politics at all,
Да может быть я по в политику вообще не
how can it be? Wait for a year now, your
ле как может быть Подождите уже год ваша
country is on your behalf, people. Say, I
страна от вашего имени людей Говорите я
don’t get involved in politics. I don’t know, maybe. Well,
не лезу в политике Я не знаю может Ну а
who attacked whom in this
кто на кого напал в этом
conflict, I have to  to
конфликте я должен в этом
figure this out But you didn’t want to
разбираться А вот вы за год не захотели
figure it out in a year, no, because you didn’t [ __ ]
разобраться нет потому что нере срали
on it Yes, so that the
в Да чтобы потре
Ukrainians will treat me like a
Украинцы будут относиться ко мне к
Russian I know that not everyone is
русскому Я знаю что все ну не все есть
good Russian, oh, or rather, there are Ukrainians
хорошие русские ой украинцы точнее есть
who are right behind  Ukraine is being drowned and the
которые прямо вот за Украину топят и
Russians are being sent unpacking, that is,
русских посылают распаковку то есть
look, you’ve been living in Russia for a year Your
смотри ты год живёшь в России Твоя
country is a year of people in Ukraine,
страна год людей в Украине тебе в этом
you won’t bother figuring this out Yes, but you’re bothering to use
разобраться ты не запарь Да но ты
roulette and search to follow What
утруждает рулетку и поис следовать Какой
percentage of Ukrainians will send you to
процент украинцев тебя будут посылать на
yes Uh-huh Yes, why don’t you  do you want to
да Угу Да а почему вот ты не хочешь в
spend this time in order to
это потратить это время для того чтобы
figure out why your country
разобраться всё-таки за что твоя страна
attacked
короче напала на
Ukraine? Probably because I’m too
Украину Наверное потому что я слишком
stupid to understand something. It’s good if
глуп Чтобы что-то понимать Хорошо если
you’re too stupid to  to understand something,
ты слишком глуп Чтобы что-то понимать то
why are you going out to take the opinion of the Ukrainians
зачем ты выходишь взять мнение украинцев
if you are stupid? You won’t understand anything, no,
если Ты глуп Ты же не поймёшь ничего нет
well, I understand that they are
ну я пойму что они меня допустим
sending me somewhere. Yes, well, we need to understand
посылают куда по Да ну на Надо же понять
the reason, for example, why the Ukrainians don’t
причину например Почему украинцы не
send the Kazakhs. Yes, but they do, wait,
посылают казахов Да а посылают подожди
wait, because  this is all A complicated
стой потому что это всё Запутанная
story, someone says that we attacked
история кто-то говорит что мы напали на
you, someone says that the Ukrainians attacked
вас кто-то говорит что украинцы напали
us, it’s hard to tell here I don’t know who to
на нас здесь не разбери Я не знаю кому
believe me Yes, really look  in a year or
верить мне Да реально смотри за год да
in a year you can’t figure it out at all And in general it’s
за год вообще не разбери И вообще это
difficult to figure it out It’s incomprehensible to the brain you
сложно разобраться Это для мозга
understand how to turn on
непостижимо понимаешь это как включить
the computer and a bunch of windows like
компьютер и там выскочили кучи окон типа
And you don’t know how to do it but
А ты не знаешь как с этим делать но
uh, I can’t understand Ukraine either,
ээ вот Украин я не могу тоже понять
see Why are my compatriots
смотри Почему мои соотечественники
Ukrainians  in chatroulette they don’t call
украинцы в чатрулетке не обзывают
Kazakhs names, they don’t call Lithuanians names, but they
казахов не обзывают литовцев а русских
call Russians names. Why,
обзывают Почему
unfortunately, I don’t know because they were
так к сожалению не знаю потому что
probably allegedly attacked. That is, you probably
наверно напали якобы о То есть наверное
see that it’s not easy  so people from
видите что это не просто так люди из
Ukraine have a negative attitude towards people from
Украины негативно относятся к людям из
Russia
России
True Well, yes, who is to blame for the fact that
Правда Ну да да кто виноват в том что
people from Ukraine have a negative attitude towards
люди из Украины негативно относятся к
people from Russia wait now the PTA
людям из России подожди сейчас ПТА
will put me against their own or that I’m not
меня против своих поставит или что я не
me I’m asking Just who is to blame for
я я я спрашиваю Просто вот кто виноват в
this  people from Ukraine have a negative
том что люди из Украины негативно
attitude towards people from Russia, I don’t know
относятся к людям из России я не знаю Ну
Well, let’s think about who is to blame, what is
так давай подумаем кто вино в чём
the reason for this, that they have such a bad
причина этого что они так плохо
attitude, turn on
относятся включаем
the brain again, someone says Yes Personally,
мозг опять же кто-то говорит Да Лично у
I have a lot of people who tell me all sorts of things
меня много мне кто говорит всяку вот
Well, mostly their own  they say that  we
Ну по больше свой части говорят что мы
Russians attacked the
русские напали на
Ukrainians yes yes Well, what do you think? That’s
украинцев да да Ну а ты как думаешь Вот
who attacked whom Ukraine attacked Russia and I
кто на кого напал Украина на Россию и я
don’t think so at all Well, look, okay,
никак не считаю Ну смотри давай хорошо
let’s do it again Well, I’m just a teacher, so I’m like
давай ещё раз Попро это я просто учитель
that on my own. So I’m helping to
так сам по себе такой Так я вот помогаю
turn on the brain Look,  if you lived in
включать мозг Вот смотри если вы жили в
Russia and your troops in Russia, we lived in
России и ваши войска в России мы жили в
Ukraine and Our troops in Ukraine, the troops of
Украине и Наши войска в Украине войска
Ukraine, not Roy Russia, came to
Украины не Ро а вой России пришли в
Ukraine, then who attacked whom, we
Украину то кто на кого напал мы
get to see the training is very
получается видишь обучение это очень
simple, that is, we  take it and look,
просто то есть мы берём и смотрим так
so here it was, Russian troops came to
тут так так было войска России пришли в
Ukraine, then who attacked whom, it’s clear that
Украину то кто на кого напал ясно что
Russia is in Ukraine everything And
Россия на Украи всё А ели
they ate Come on, I love it when a person’s IOC turns on
те Давай люблю когда включается МОК
Come on It’s always on It’s just that it’s
Давай Он всегда включен Просто он тупит
stupid If they say that I’m allowed to drown
поно Если те скажу что я допустим топлю
not for  Russia for y for America I’m not
не за Россию за у за Америку Я же не
saying who you’re drowning for, we want to, I
говорю за кого ты топишь мы вот хотим Я
want to understand in your head Who is
хочу понять в твоей голове Кто
to blame We have found out we are dumb, that is, who is
виноват Мы выяснили немы то есть кто
to blame for the fact that Ukrainians
виноват в том что украинцы плохо
treat Russians badly, it turns out that
относятся к россиянам мы получается да
we are
мы это кто русские всё россияне Да
this is who the Russians are, all the Russians Yes, they are to blame for the fact that the Ukrainians have a bad attitude But what else do you want to find out the Ukrainians here in the entrance Poor about the Bad about the crowns some are Trusted Simply no Simply Normal there are adequate Ukrainians good for example You calculated something percentage I have friends who lived in Kyiv and still keep in touch with me Well look, for example, you thought it was okay for me  belongs to the Ukrainians,
мне нормально ещё относится у украинцев
it means everything needs to move out of this Well, from
значит всё нужно съезжать с этой Ну с
chat roulette And if they have a bad attitude, then
чат рулетки А если плохо относятся то
what to continue to finish off this whole one,
что продолжать добивать вот эту всю
which one to finish off, how to find out which one
какую добивать как
again, look again That is, you
какую узнавать ещё раз смотри То есть ты
already understand that your country attacked
уже понимаешь что твоя страна напала на
my country You understand that you are to blame
мою страну Ты понимаешь что вы виноваты
for  the fact that you also attacked people in Ukraine,
в том что вы напали и у людей в Украине
but instead of communicating with
но ты вместо того чтобы общаться со
your Russians,
своими россиянами
nya under Poche, you behave so badly Veta and
ня при Поче вы так плохо себя Вете и
somehow change this behavior, you waste
как-то изменить это поведение ты тратишь
your energy on dragons  Ukrainians
свои сил на того чтобы дракони украинцев
Yes, but no one is dragoning them, I don’t wish harm
Да а никто их не драконит я зла не желаю
Well, that is, look, you come So, in
Ну то есть смотри ты приходишь Так им
short, there’s something there, you look at how they
короче там что-то смотришь как они там
call you names, you know it all, for
тебя обзывают это всё знаешь вот маньяк
example, a maniac, for example, adj.
например
dad, mom, and to the girl
прил папу маму так и к девочке
avoca them lo
авока их ло
just look at the candy Do you want
просто конфетку смотри Хочешь
candy how will the girl
конфетку как будет девочка к тебе
treat you if you came home to mom and
относиться если ты прил домой папу и
dad candy how the girl will be those relatively
маму конфетку как девочка будет те отно
negatively look said you
негативно смотри сказал ты ничего
didn’t do anything wrong yes you
плохого е не сделал да ты конфетку даже
you even offer candy, you want to talk and she
предлагаешь хочешь поговорить а она
understands that you are mom and dad
понимает что ты е папу и маму
and it turns out that you want to say that I
и мер получается ты хочешь сказать что я
just took it right now and attacked
вот прямо вот взял сейчас и напал на
Ukraine, right now I took it and
Украину вот прямо вот сейчас взял и
attacked Ukraine, so I did
напал на Украину так оно получа ещё раз
n’t understand it again. Well, you tell me  you say that
не понял Ну ты мне говоришь то что якобы
I’m supposedly like someone’s parents, in short, and the
я как типа чьих-то родителей короче и
girl of the same girl to whom I
девочки этой же девочки которой я вот
supposedly naturally give candy like that
якобы естественно даю конфетку типа вот
and like I’m saying
и типа говорю
there like Hello, the
там типа Привет
Russian people attacked the Ukrainian
российский народ напал на украинский
people. What’s not clear here? No, you
народ Да что тут непонятно Не ну ты
want  to say that I am involved in this Well,
хочешь сказать что я в этом причаст Ну
yes, you are a representative of the Russian people, and
да ты представитель российского народа а
if I say that I have two nations, well, two
если я скажу что у меня две нации ну две
nations, are you a representative of the Russian
нации ты представитель российского
people and that yes or no Partially Yes,
народа и что да или нет Частично Да вот
well, you are a citizen of the Russian Federation
ну ты Ты гражданин Российской Федерации
Well, I am everything, you are a citizen of the
Ну являюсь всё являешься гражданином
Russian Federation power  here it
Российской Федерации власть здесь
is authorized by whom the citizens of the Russian
уполномочена кем гражданами Российской
Federation yes, that is, it acts on
Федерации да то есть она действует от
your behalf Yes it fulfills everything of the
вашего имени Да она исполняет все
people of the Russian Federation on behalf of the people of the
народа Российской Федерации имени народа
Russian Federation if the people of the
Российской Федерации если народ
Russian Federation are silent So that means
Российской Федерации молчит Так значит
they agree passively agree with the
он соглашается пассивно соглашается с
actions of their authorities then  there is
действиями своей власти то есть
supports this war, that is, you personally,
поддерживает эту войну то есть ты лично
right now, will support this war,
конкретно сейчас поддержишь эту войну
Ukraine means to me, according to your words, I
Украине значит мне по твоим словам Мне
need to come out and say
нужно выйти сказать
what kind of
какого
stealing and war specifically you are not just
укра и войну конкретно ты не просто
Putin, because Putin is from somewhere, that is,
Путин так потому что Путин откуда то
I am here, yes, yes, yes,
есть я вот я да
yes,
вот да ты
strange, wait strange  there
странно подожди странно на моих руках ни
wasn’t a single one on my hands no look on your
одного не было нет смотри на твоих
hands again look come on so who
руках ещё раз смотри давай так кто
elects your president and your
избирает вашего президента и ваших
deputies who make decisions Come on
депутатов которые принимают решени Давай
Vela man Who elects your
велы человек Кто избирает ваших
deputies and the
депутатов и
president who beat a
президента кто изби
Well supposedly we yes Well you
а Ну якобы мы да Ну ты
you elect, as a citizen, you elect another
избирает ты как граж ты е другого ещё
again, look at the other, not the other, you
раз смотри другого не другого это уже
will already complain at the Nyurba trial
будете жаловаться на нюрбинском процессе
that we didn’t have another like this, look,
что у нас другого не было такого смотри
you elected the Germans, elected Hitler, and
вы избрали немцы избрали Гитлера также
he acted on their behalf, the people elected
он действовал от их имени люди избрали
Putin, he acts on their behalf, so in
Путина Он действует от их имени так в
democratic  countries, if the actions of the
демократических странах если действия
president there do not coincide with the interests of
там президента не совпадает с интерес
society, society goes out to some kind of
общества общество выходит на какие-то
demonstrations, so it somehow
там демонстрации так она как-то
shows that it does not agree with
показывает что оно не согласно так с
these actions in Russia, I see that
этими действиями в России я вижу что
there are no
нету
disagreement of society, on the
какие-то несогласия общества так есть
contrary, that society is supported by
наоборот что общество это поддерживает
someone actively, someone passively, yes, that
кто-то активно кто-то пассивно да то
is, in the Criminal Code there is also such a
есть в Уголовном кодексе есть ещё такое
concept as complicity, yes, that is, for example, you
понятие соучастие да то есть ты например
looked, yes, like, but didn’t take
смотрел да типа но не предпринимал
any action, too,
Никаких действий тоже там
look,
вот смотри
you now understand
ты сейчас понимаешь
what’s what  your
что что твоя
country
страна
sent soldiers, tanks, guns, yes,
отправила солдат танки пушки Да людей в
it sent people in my country on your
моей стране она отправила от твоего
behalf, not on behalf of Putin, not on behalf of
имени не от имени Путина не от имени там
some Volodin, yes, they are on behalf of
какого-то Володина Да они от имени
the Russians because they act, they are
российского потому что они действуют они
temporary, these acting duties
временные эти исполняющие обязанности
positions so they act on
своей должности так они действуют от
behalf of the Russian people so
имени российского народа так
specifically Putin us the Russian people
конкретно Путин нас российский народ в
including you Uh-huh Well I just don’t understand
том числе и ты Угу Ну только не понимаю
how I’m involved in this
как я к этому
I didn’t even serve again let’s do it
причасти я даже не служил ещё раз давай
again uh I understand you the Russian
ещё раз ээ я я тебя понял российский
people but I have nothing to do with them  not involved I
народ но я к нем никак не причастен Я
never
никогда не
served in the army at all like China to be
служил нед армии вообще как Китай если
honest Let's look again so I'm
честно Давай ещё раз посмотрим так что я
not let's say so when uh for example
не являюсь давай так когда ээ например
uh
ээ
Russia receives some material
Россия получает какие-то материальные
benefits so it distributes it among its
блага так оно распределяет е среди своих
citizens
граждан
so yes When Russia  does something So
так да Когда Россия делает какую-то Так
who is responsible for this,
кто несёт за это
citizens have nothing to do with it,
ответственность граждане не при чём да
it turns out hard, it’s hard to understand
получается тяжело тяжело это понимать
that Yes, that you are responsible, you have to admit it to
что Да что ты ответственный это надо
yourself, then you won’t be able to be
себе тогда ты не сможешь быть
neutral Why is it I will always be
нейтральне Почему это я буду всегда
neutral not if you understand that you are to
нейтраль не если ты поймёшь что ты
blame for this  and your neighbor
виноват в этом и твой сосед
is to blame, you attacked
виноват вы напали на
Ukraine Well, it turns out,
Украину Ну получается
but again, supposedly if we attacked Okay with
а опять же якобы если мы напали Ладно с
him What should we do Well, like we need to
ним Что нам сделать Ну типа нам нужно
retreat supposedly or that this is already the
отступать якобы или что это уже сейчас
second question Yes you will What to do Yes and the
второй вопрос Да будешь Что делать Да а
first We understood that you are
первое Мы понимали что ты несёшь
responsible
ответствен
Utvo with responsibility girls Yes, all of you,
утво со ответственность девуш Да вы все
Citizens of the Russian Federation, are not
Граждане Российской Федерации нете
responsible for this attack
ответственность за это нападение потому
because the government is acting on your behalf, you
что власть действует от вашего имени вы
are elmo, it’s not the aliens who put you in
елмо это не инопланетяне поставили вам
power, it’s you who put
власть это вы поставили активно или
your position in an active or passive position. So now
пассивной своей позиции Так теперь
the question is what to do. What are your
вопрос что делать Вот какие у тебя есть
options? What  can be done in such a
варианты Что можно делать в такой
situation when we realized that you are to blame,
ситуации когда мы поняли что вы виновато
this is IS
это
I need and everything that VSK means Well, as
ис Мне нужно и всё что значит ВСК Ну как
in the sense of Vienna,
в смысле Вена
there is a damn different solution Yes, according to your
там решение блин другое Да по твоим
words, in principle, Come on, think about it
словам в принципе Давай давай подумай
other, how else can I influence the situation?
другое как ещё можно влиять на ситуацию
Well, how else can I influence the situation
Ну как я ещё могу повлиять на ситуацию
if nothing changes at all in
ес если вообще ничего не изменится в
this world? Well, that means a rally can be a
этом мире А ну значит по митинге можно и
rally if if you have the courage to
митинг если если у тебя есть смелость
go out, but I think you don’t have the courage. What
выходить но я думаю нету смелости Какие
other versions are there then?
ещё есть тогда версии
other countries Yes, just running away to
в другие страны Да убежать просто в
another country is also not well, just
другую страну тоже это не ну просто
running away And that How the war has changed
убежал И что Как изменилась война
is changing Well, how are you, come on now, your
меняется Ну как ты давай сейчас тво твои
words Come on, now I’ll tell you the
слова Давай давай теперь я тебе расскажу
algorithm, look, if you were wasting
алгоритм смотри если бы ты тратил сейчас
time now, at least here you are I understand what’s there
время хотя бы вот ты Я понимаю что там у
you don't have  some kind of courage of
тебя нету какой-то там смелости
political activity, you won’t
политической активности ты не будешь
go anywhere with a poster, so with
выходить никуда с плакатом так с
rallies, you’re afraid of it, it’s not yours at all,
митингами ты это боишься это вообще не
but since you’re going out to chat roulette,
твоё но раз ты выходишь в чат рулетку У
you have the time
тебя есть врем
and knowledge of how to do it in Russian, in short, the time and
и нание как это по-русски короче время и
desire to go to Char roulette  and communicate
желание выходить в Ча рулетку и общаться
with people like this, if instead
с людьми так если бы ты вместо того
of going out and choosing Ukraine,
чтобы выходить и выбирать Украину на
which you attacked and your neighbors, you would go out
которую ты напал и твои соседи выходил
to Roulette with the Russians with
бы в Рулетку с русскими со
yours, I
своими этими
would like to convince my own people, even for
ждана переубедить своих даже вот да
example  would communicate and why are we fighting in
например общался бы а зачем мы воюем в
Ukraine like this and Is it really there on
Украине так а Действительно ли там на
This is all nonsense that they
Вот это всё бред который нам
tell us so why our people are dying and
разговаривают так за что умирают наши и
that is, we need to change public
вот то есть надо менять общественное
opinion, you can’t go to a rally I
мнение ты не можешь выйти на митинг Я
understand that you have never done this
понимаю так ты никогда этим не занимался
for you  it’s generally scary, like, well, you
для тебя это вообще страшно типа ну и ты
don’t see it, but
не видишь в этом но изменять
you can change public opinion. You
общественное мнение ты можешь Ты же
sit at roulette for days, for example, and you
сидишь в рулетке днями например да и
spend time studying what
тратишь время на то чтобы изучать какой
percentage of Ukrainians,
процент украинцев
uh, hate you there as a Russian, but
ээ ненавидит там тебя как русского а
Try to go to Russian roulette and
Попробуй зайти в российскую рулетку и
study what percentage of people
поиз учать Какой процент людей
support this war in Ukraine and you
поддерживает эту войну в Украине и ты
will be surprised and then you will think about
будешь удивлён и тогда будешь подумай
whether you can reduce this percentage if
Можешь ли ты уменьшить этот процент если
you, uh, communicating just like Russian with
ты ээ общаясь вот просто как русский с
Russian, uh, you’ll make someone
русским да э заставишь кого-то
think that maybe not  you have to go to
задуматься что может не надо лезть в
Ukraine to kill people Yes, with this you can
Украину убивать людей Да ты этим сможешь
save someone in Russia and save
спасти кого-то и в России и спасти
someone in
кого-то в
Ukraine This is the position That is, you
Украине Вот это и есть позиция То есть
need to understand that yes I am responsible  for
надо понять что да Я ответственный за
this you have to think about what to do to
это и надо думать что делать чтобы
change no one says come on
изменить никто не говорит что давай
out. You won’t go to a rally.
выходи На митинг ты не выйдешь На митинг
I understand that you’ve never gone
я понимаю ты никогда в жизни не выходил
to a rally in your life and you won’t go now. This is
на митинг так и сейчас не выйдешь Это
something so far away for you
для тебя что-то вообще далёкое такое так
and so scary.  No, I’m not afraid of death, yes,
и страшное так Нет я не боюсь смерти да
don’t you dare? That is, here’s some advice for you,
Не посмеешь То есть тебе вот наважки
in short, eh, just going to a rally in
короче э просто вот выйти на митинг
public to say something is scary.
публично сказать какую-то это страшно
For many, Yes, I’m not afraid, I
Для многих Да мне не страшно мне в
don’t want to go to prison, everything is scary,
тюрьму не охота садиться всё ну страшно
for example, the fear of prison doesn’t matter there.
например страх тюрьмы там неважно
I understand that  wait, wait, if
Я понимаю что это подожди стой если бы
I were scared, if I were
мне было бы страшно если бы мне было бы
scared, I probably wouldn’t do this, but
страшно Наверное я бы этого не делал Но
I can do it calmly, look,
я могу это сделать спокойно смотри я
in short, look, come on, you don’t see
короче смотри Давай так ты не видишь
the point of the country, it doesn’t matter, I know that you
смысла стра неважно так я знаю что ты
won’t do it all for  That’s
этого не будешь зделать всё для меня это
enough for me now, but sitting in chat
сейчас достаточно но сидеть в чат
roulette and instead of talking to the
рулетке и вместо того чтобы говорить с
Ukrainians, talk to the Russians and
украинцами говорить с россиянами и
try to sow the grain for them. What, let’s say we don’t
пробовать им посеять зерно Что скажем не
need this war, so this is Dava’s other thing; he
надо этой войны так вот это Дава другое
won’t listen to me right away. Why
меня слушать сразу уже не будет Почему
Well?  like some Russian bastard is
Ну как какой-то русский [__] что-то
talking about something, well look, you look like a
там базарит поди Ну смотри ты как
Russian I’m from Ukraine and then with people from
русский Я из Украины и то с людьми с
Russia They listen to me then if you’re Russian with a
России Меня слушают то если ты русский с
Russian Why won’t they
русским Почему тебя не будут
listen to you Well, what do you think they’ll
слушать Ну а что меня будут думаешь
listen to me I’m one person alone  a person, and
слушать я один человек один человек да и
you communicate with someone, also the same and
ты общаешься с кем-то тоже одним и
different. There are people, there is some girl, a
разные Есть люди есть какая-то девочка
student, and there is some
студентка так есть какой-то дядька
older guy, there is someone else, someone. Yes, he
старший есть кто-то ещё кто-то Да
listens, he will think about it if you spent
послушает задумается если ты бы тратил
you  and you’ll do the same and you’ll tell someone
ты и будешь так также и кому-то скажешь
like I’m telling you now that maybe we should, uh,
Вот как я тебе сейчас что может надо ээ
not just sit there in chat roulette, but
не просто там сидеть в чат рулетке а
tell our citizens from Russia
нашим гражданам из России рассказывать
that Well, let’s not do it. There’s no need to
что Ну давай не надо Вот не надо
come and say, let’s all stop
приходить и говорить давай всё прекратим
the war, just start talking
войну вот Начни просто разговоры
questions yes Why are we
вопросами да А зачем мы там
fighting there Why do we need this war as citizens of
воюем Зачем нам эта война как гражданам
Russia so that people think Yes
России вот чтобы люди задумывались Да
if they say there We try there
если они говорят там Мы там пробуй Вот
Talk you will learn to convey
разговаривай ты научишься ээ доносить
your opinion Yes and a person when you
свои мнение Да и человек когда ты
you say another will say a third in someone’s
скажешь другой скажет третий у кого-то в
head it will switch for everyone it won’t
голове переключится у всех не
switch but for a certain part Yes
переключится но у определённой части Да
And the more people are against this
И вот чем больше людей будет против этой
war against this special operation and the
войны против этой спецоперации да тем
faster peace will come If you spent
быстрее наступит мир Если бы ты тратил
that much energy How much do you spend in chat
столько энергии Сколько ты тратишь в чат
roulette on  conversations with Ukrainians
рулетке на разговоры с украинцами Если
If you spent at least part of it
бы ты это тратил хотя бы часть её на
talking with your fellow tribesmen Yes,
разговор со своими соплеменниками Да
who support this war,
которые поддерживают вот эту войну так
then everything could change, you know,
тогда бы всё может изменилось понимаешь
yeah, you promise me that you will choose
угу обещаешь мне что будешь выбирать
now  in even roulette Russia and not
теперь в чет рулетки Россию а не
Ukraine You think I listened to you
Украину Вот ты думаешь я тебя послушал
all that Well, I’m asking you promise,
всё что Ну я вот спрашиваю ты обеща вот
I want to understand or you wait, why should I
я хочу понять или ты подожди а зачем мне
promise
пообещать
if I’ve already talked to my fellow tribesmen As you
если я со своими соплеменниками Как ты
say Well, look, I do
говоришь разговаривал уже Ну вот смотри
n’t want to understand Pony  majority
не вот хочу понять Поня большинство
part majority
часть большинство
part Ukraine On the contrary, let's do it like this
часть Украину Наоборот за давай так ещё
again, you and I have separated you and I,
раз ты вот мы с тобой
choose from roulette Ukraine
разъединил выбирать в от рулетки Украину
No matter what,
Да что бы нет
unteachable, that's right Yes,
необучаемый всё верно Да
come on
давай
unteachable like this Glory to Ukraine but I
необучаемый вот так Слава Украине но я
believe that it’s
верю что даже
so easy to reach even unrealistically stupid people,
до нереально тупых людей доходить так
you need doba doba doba and doba Oh so
просто треба доба доба доба и доба О так
Ale, in short, yes, you won’t
Але короче да е деяки что до них не
reach them, I think VN will think about it VN
дойде я думаю ВН то задумается ВН втик
because it’s hard for me to think so because
тому что му тяжело думати так тому что
viznavati sob scho mukha Tse is hard Write to
визнавати соб що муха Це тяжело Пиши на
my Telegram directly at the same time axis VN
мий Telegram прямо зараз ось ВН
apok tse duzhe and  very respectfully YouTube has taken
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg Orcs in your ban and even
нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и дуже
more videos I don’t show people often I don’t
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams For this purpose,
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we need Mali to write an operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
right away and Popik is there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegram okrim video also tezh tsikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and we  blame you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independent in  togo show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава Украине пись
with
с